A Guide to the Papers of Edward L. Schrock, 1999-2004
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Correspondence 1999-2004
  - Letters from Constituents 1999-2004
    - Clean Energy August 2001 (Box-folder 8:51)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation August 2001 (Box-folder 8:52)
    - Education Bill August 2001 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Employment Non-Discrimination Act (ENDA) August 2001 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Environment August 2001 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) August 2001 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Equal Protection of Voting Rights Act August 2001 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Family Planning August 2001 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Gun Control August 2001 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Internet Freedom and Broadband Deployment Act August 2001 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Israel August 2001 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Jet Noise August 2001 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Kadeer, Rebiya August 2001 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Low Frequency Active (LFA) Sonar August 2001 (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Marijuana, Hemp, and Other Illegal Drugs August 2001 (Box-folder 9:13)
    - Medicare August 2001 (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Men's Health August 2001 (Box-folder 9:15)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits August 2001 (Box-folder 9:16)
    - Missiles August 2001 (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Napster August 2001 (Box-folder 9:18)
    - National Defense Authorization Bill August 2001 (Box-folder 9:19)
    - Retirement Age for Pilots August 2001 (Box-folder 9:20)
    - Roadless Area Conservation Rule August 2001 (Box-folder 9:21)
    - Social Security August 2001 (Box-folder 9:22)
    - Taxes August 2001 (Box-folder 9:23)
    - Tricare Coverage for Military Retirees August 2001 (Box-folder 9:24)
    - Windfall Elimination Provision August 2001 (Box-folder 9:25)
    - Working Lands Stewardship Act August 2001 (Box-folder 9:26)
    - Various August 2001 (Box-folder 9:27)
    - 9-11 Terrorist Attack September 2001 (Box-folder 9:28)
    - Abortion September 2001 (Box-folder 9:29)
    - Airline Workers September 2001 (Box-folder 9:30)
    - Airport Security September 2001 (Box-folder 9:31)
    - Environment September 2001 (Box-folder 9:32)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) September 2001 (Box-folder 9:33)
    - Family Planning September 2001 (Box-folder 9:34)
    - Farm Bill September 2001 (Box-folder 9:35)
    - Gay Rights September 2001 (Box-folder 9:36)
    - Gun Control September 2001 (Box-folder 9:37)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits September 2001 (Box-folder 9:38)
    - Privacy Rights September 2001 (Box-folder 9:39)
    - Realty Regulations September 2001 (Box-folder 9:40)
    - Roadless Area Conservation Rule September 2001 (Box-folder 9:41)
    - Various September 2001 (Box-folder 9:42)
    - 9-11 Terrorist Attack October 2001 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Abortion October 2001 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Airlines October 2001 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Airport Security October 2001 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation I October 2001 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation II October 2001 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation III October 2001 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Economic Stimulus Package October 2001 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Environment October 2001 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Fast Track Trade Bills October 2001 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - House Closing / Anthrax Scare October 2001 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Illegal Aliens October 2001 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Information Leaks October 2001 (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Israel October 2001 (Box-folder 10:14)
    - Medicare October 2001 (Box-folder 10:15)
    - Military Surplus October 2001 (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Public Schools October 2001 (Box-folder 10:17)
    - Safe and Stable Families Programs October 2001 (Box-folder 10:18)
    - Small Business Emergency Relief Act October 2001 (Box-folder 10:19)
    - Stem Cell Research October 2001 (Box-folder 10:20)
    - Travel America Now Act October 2001 (Box-folder 10:21)
    - Various October 2001 (Box-folder 10:22)
    - 9-11 Terrorist Attack November 2001 (Box-folder 10:23)
    - Airport Security November 2001 (Box-folder 10:24)
    - CARA Land Grab Bill November 2001 (Box-folder 10:25)
    - Clean Energy November 2001 (Box-folder 10:26)
    - Customs Border Security Act November 2001 (Box-folder 10:27)
    - Economic Stimulus Bill November 2001 (Box-folder 10:28)
    - Email Tax November 2001 (Box-folder 10:29)
    - Family Planning November 2001 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Fast Track Trade Bill November 2001 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Gun Control November 2001 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Houses of Worship Political Speech Protection Act November 2001 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Illegal Aliens November 2001 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Marijuana, Hemp, and Other Illegal Drugs November 2001 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Medical Research November 2001 (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Medicare November 2001 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Military Tribunals November 2001 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits November 2001 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - National Defense Authorization Bill November 2001 (Box-folder 11:11)
    - Privacy Rights November 2001 (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Railroad Retirement Reform November 2001 (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Realty Regulations November 2001 (Box-folder 11:14)
    - Safe and Stable Families Programs November 2001 (Box-folder 11:15)
    - School Prayer November 2001 (Box-folder 11:16)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan November 2001 (Box-folder 11:17)
    - Taxes November 2001 (Box-folder 11:18)
    - Terrorism Insurance November 2001 (Box-folder 11:19)
    - Travel America Now Act November 2001 (Box-folder 11:20)
    - Truthfulness, Responsibility, and Accountability in Contracting Act (TRAC) November 2001 (Box-folder 11:21)
    - Unemployment November 2001 (Box-folder 11:22)
    - Various November 2001 (Box-folder 11:23)
    - Airport Security December 2001 (Box-folder 11:24)
    - Cloning December 2001 (Box-folder 11:25)
    - Email Tax December 2001 (Box-folder 11:26)
    - Federal Employees Health Benefits Program (FEHBP) premiums December 2001 (Box-folder 11:27)
    - Federal Nurse Traineeship December 2001 (Box-folder 11:28)
    - Gay Marriage December 2001 (Box-folder 11:29)
    - Illegal Aliens December 2001 (Box-folder 11:30)
    - Industrial Hemp December 2001 (Box-folder 11:31)
    - Israel December 2001 (Box-folder 11:32)
    - Medicare December 2001 (Box-folder 11:33)
    - Public Schools December 2001 (Box-folder 11:34)
    - Railroad Retirement Reform December 2001 (Box-folder 11:35)
    - Social Security Act December 2001 (Box-folder 11:36)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996 December 2001 (Box-folder 11:37)
    - United Nations December 2001 (Box-folder 11:38)
    - Various December 2001 (Box-folder 11:39)
    - Airline Workers 2001 (Box-folder 11:40)
    - Airport Security 2001 (Box-folder 11:41)
    - Animal Rights 2001 (Box-folder 11:42)
    - Black Berets 2001 (Box-folder 11:43)
    - Campaign Finance Reform 2001 (Box-folder 11:44)
    - Ergonomics 2001 (Box-folder 11:45)
    - Federal Employees Health Benefits Program (FEHBP) premiums 2001 (Box-folder 11:46)
    - Gun Control 2001 (Box-folder 11:47)
    - Interstate Waste 2001 (Box-folder 11:48)
    - Marijuana 2001 (Box-folder 11:49)
    - Mexican Trucks 2001 (Box-folder 11:50)
    - Northwest Branch of Crab Creek Dredging Project 2001 (Box-folder 11:51)
    - Pension Reform 2001 (Box-folder 11:52)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996 2001 (Box-folder 11:53)
    - Travel America Now Act 2001 (Box-folder 11:54)
    - UFO's and Extraterrestrials 2001 (Box-folder 11:55)
    - Various 2001 (Box-folder 11:56)
    - Campaign Finance Reform January 2002 (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation January 2002 (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Gay Marriage January 2002 (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Navy Outlaying Landing Field in Perquimans County, NC January 2002 (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Various January 2002 (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Abortion February 2002 (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Campaign Finance Reform February 2002 (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation February 2002 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Manufacturing Extension Partnership February 2002 (Box-folder 12:9)
    - Pork Barrel Spending February 2002 (Box-folder 12:10)
    - Telecommunications Act of 1996 February 2002 (Box-folder 12:11)
    - Various February 2002 (Box-folder 12:12)
    - Airline Security March 2002 (Box-folder 12:13)
    - Campaign Finance Reform March 2002 (Box-folder 12:14)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation March 2002 (Box-folder 12:15)
    - Fisheries Recovery Act March 2002 (Box-folder 12:16)
    - Higher Education Act, Drug Offenses March 2002 (Box-folder 12:17)
    - Medicare March 2002 (Box-folder 12:18)
    - Postal Competition March 2002 (Box-folder 12:19)
    - Realty Regulations March 2002 (Box-folder 12:20)
    - Social Security March 2002 (Box-folder 12:21)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan March 2002 (Box-folder 12:22)
    - Taxes March 2002 (Box-folder 12:23)
    - Welfare Reform March 2002 (Box-folder 12:24)
    - Various March 2002 (Box-folder 12:25)
    - Abortion April 2002 (Box-folder 12:26)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation April 2002 (Box-folder 12:27)
    - Fair Use / Copyright Laws April 2002 (Box-folder 12:28)
    - Illegal Aliens April 2002 (Box-folder 12:29)
    - Israel April 2002 (Box-folder 12:30)
    - Jet Noise at Oceana April 2002 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Medicare April 2002 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits April 2002 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Privacy Rights April 2002 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Public Schools April 2002 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Recreational Waters Protection Act April 2002 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Religion and Politics April 2002 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Taxes April 2002 (Box-folder 13:8)
    - Tax Exemption for Clergy Housing April 2002 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - United Nations April 2002 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Welfare Reform April 2002 (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Various April 2002 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Airlines May 2002 (Box-folder 13:13)
    - Airline Security May 2002 (Box-folder 13:14)
    - Army Corp of Engineers Reform May 2002 (Box-folder 13:15)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation May 2002 (Box-folder 13:16)
    - Diplomat Parking Fines May 2002 (Box-folder 13:17)
    - English Language May 2002 (Box-folder 13:18)
    - Fair Use / Copyright Laws May 2002 (Box-folder 13:19)
    - Family Opportunities Act May 2002 (Box-folder 13:20)
    - Foreign Aid May 2002 (Box-folder 13:21)
    - Gun Control May 2002 (Box-folder 13:22)
    - Housing Affordability Act May 2002 (Box-folder 13:23)
    - Illegal Aliens May 2002 (Box-folder 13:24)
    - Mass Transportation May 2002 (Box-folder 13:25)
    - Medicare May 2002 (Box-folder 13:26)
    - Medicaid May 2002 (Box-folder 13:27)
    - Medical Research May 2002 (Box-folder 13:28)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits May 2002 (Box-folder 13:29)
    - Nuclear Waste May 2002 (Box-folder 13:30)
    - Post Office May 2002 (Box-folder 13:31)
    - Reserve Retirement May 2002 (Box-folder 13:32)
    - Terrorism May 2002 (Box-folder 13:33)
    - United Nations May 2002 (Box-folder 13:34)
    - Various May 2002 (Box-folder 13:35)
    - Abortion June 2002 (Box-folder 13:36)
    - Airlines June 2002 (Box-folder 13:37)
    - Airline Security June 2002 (Box-folder 13:38)
    - American Horse Slaughter Prevention Act June 2002 (Box-folder 13:39)
    - American Retirement Security June 2002 (Box-folder 13:40)
    - American Sovereignty Restoration Act June 2002 (Box-folder 13:41)
    - Assistant U.S. Attorney's Retirement Benefit Equity Act June 2002 (Box-folder 13:42)
    - Blood Cancer June 2002 (Box-folder 13:43)
    - Colorectal Cancer June 2002 (Box-folder 13:44)
    - Community Character Act June 2002 (Box-folder 13:45)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation I June 2002 (Box-folder 13:46)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation II June 2002 (Box-folder 13:47)
    - Corporate Responsibility June 2002 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Death Tax June 2002 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Email Tax June 2002 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Ethanol June 2002 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - FDA Tobacco Authority Amendments Act June 2002 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Freedom to Fish Acy June 2002 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Hate Crimes June 2002 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Health Care June 2002 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Homeland Security June 2002 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Immigration June 2002 (Box-folder 14:10)
    - Israel June 2002 (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Malpractice Insurance June 2002 (Box-folder 14:12)
    - Medicare June 2002 (Box-folder 14:13)
    - Medicaid June 2002 (Box-folder 14:14)
    - Medical Research June 2002 (Box-folder 14:15)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits June 2002 (Box-folder 14:16)
    - National Monuments Fairness Act June 2002 (Box-folder 14:17)
    - Nurses June 2002 (Box-folder 14:18)
    - Pension Reform June 2002 (Box-folder 14:19)
    - Rape June 2002 (Box-folder 14:20)
    - Realty Regulations June 2002 (Box-folder 14:21)
    - Religion and Politics June 2002 (Box-folder 14:22)
    - Reserve Retirement June 2002 (Box-folder 14:23)
    - Resident-Physician Work Hours June 2002 (Box-folder 14:24)
    - SAFER Act June 2002 (Box-folder 14:25)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan June 2002 (Box-folder 14:26)
    - Syria June 2002 (Box-folder 14:27)
    - Taxes June 2002 (Box-folder 14:28)
    - Terrorism June 2002 (Box-folder 14:29)
    - United Nations June 2002 (Box-folder 14:30)
    - Welfare Reform June 2002 (Box-folder 14:31)
    - Various June 2002 (Box-folder 14:32)
    - Abortion July 2002 (Box-folder 14:33)
    - Airline Security July 2002 (Box-folder 14:34)
    - Assistant U.S. Attorney's Retirement Benefit Equity Act July 2002 (Box-folder 14:35)
    - Blood Cancer July 2002 (Box-folder 14:36)
    - Capital Punishment / Death Penalty July 2002 (Box-folder 14:37)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation July 2002 (Box-folder 14:38)
    - Consumer Rental-Purchase Agreement Act July 2002 (Box-folder 14:39)
    - Corporate Responsibility July 2002 (Box-folder 14:40)
    - Cuba July 2002 (Box-folder 14:41)
    - Domestic Partnership July 2002 (Box-folder 14:42)
    - EchoStar / DirectTV Merger July 2002 (Box-folder 14:43)
    - Employment Non-Discrimination Act (ENDA) July 2002 (Box-folder 14:44)
    - Fair Use / Copyright July 2002 (Box-folder 14:45)
    - Federal Employees Health Benefits Program (FEHBP) Premiums July 2002 (Box-folder 14:46)
    - Fishing July 2002 (Box-folder 14:47)
    - Gun Control July 2002 (Box-folder 14:48)
    - Hate Crimes July 2002 (Box-folder 14:49)
    - Homeland Security July 2002 (Box-folder 14:50)
    - Immigration July 2002 (Box-folder 14:51)
    - Internet Radio July 2002 (Box-folder 14:52)
    - Iraq July 2002 (Box-folder 14:53)
    - Israel July 2002 (Box-folder 14:54)
    - Medical Research July 2002 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Medicare July 2002 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits July 2002 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - Naturally Occurring Retirement Communities (NORCS) July 2002 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Public Schools July 2002 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Rape July 2002 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Reserve Retirement July 2002 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Saudi Arabia July 2002 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - Social Security July 2002 (Box-folder 15:9)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan July 2002 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Various July 2002 (Box-folder 15:11)
    - Abortion August 2002 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - Contract Termination for Integrated Warfare System August 2002 (Box-folder 15:13)
    - Gun Control August 2002 (Box-folder 15:14)
    - Immigration August 2002 (Box-folder 15:15)
    - Iraq August 2002 (Box-folder 15:16)
    - Prescription Drugs August 2002 (Box-folder 15:17)
    - Prescription Drugs August 2002 (Box-folder 15:18)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation September 2002 (Box-folder 15:19)
    - Fishing September 2002 (Box-folder 15:20)
    - Immigration September 2002 (Box-folder 15:21)
    - Iraq September 2002 (Box-folder 15:22)
    - Medical Research September 2002 (Box-folder 15:23)
    - Medicare September 2002 (Box-folder 15:24)
    - Prescription Drugs September 2002 (Box-folder 15:25)
    - Various September 2002 (Box-folder 15:26)
    - Catholic Services at Fort Story October 2002 (Box-folder 15:27)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation October 2002 (Box-folder 15:28)
    - Corporate Responsiblity October 2002 (Box-folder 15:29)
    - Federal Parole October 2002 (Box-folder 15:30)
    - Iraq October 2002 (Box-folder 15:31)
    - Medicare October 2002 (Box-folder 15:32)
    - Navy Aircraft Carrier October 2002 (Box-folder 15:33)
    - Windfall Elimination Provision October 2002 (Box-folder 15:34)
    - Various October 2002 (Box-folder 15:35)
    - Corporate Responsibility November 2002 (Box-folder 15:36)
    - FCC / Amateur Radio November 2002 (Box-folder 15:37)
    - Homeland Security November 2002 (Box-folder 15:38)
    - Medicare November 2002 (Box-folder 15:39)
    - Perkins Act / Pell Grants November 2002 (Box-folder 15:40)
    - Career and Technical Education December 2002 (Box-folder 15:41)
    - Head Start Program December 2002 (Box-folder 15:42)
    - Abstinence Until Marriage Education 2002 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Airlines 2002 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Airport Security 2002 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Campaign Finance Reform 2002 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation 2002 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Immigration 2002 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Israel 2002 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Medicare 2002 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Nurses 2002 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Pork Barrel Spending 2002 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - Realty Regulations 2002 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Reserve Retirement 2002 (Box-folder 16:12)
    - Social Security 2002 (Box-folder 16:13)
    - Terrorism 2002 (Box-folder 16:14)
    - Welfare Reform 2002 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - Various 2002 (Box-folder 16:16)
    - Social Security / Medicare January 2003 (Box-folder 16:17)
    - Various January 2003 (Box-folder 16:18)
    - Various February 2003 (Box-folder 16:19)
    - Social Security March 2003 (Box-folder 16:20)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan I March 2003 (Box-folder 16:21)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan II March 2003 (Box-folder 16:22)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan III March 2003 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan IV March 2003 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan V March 2003 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan VI March 2003 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan VII March 2003 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan VIII March 2003 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan IX March 2003 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan X March 2003 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XI March 2003 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XII March 2003 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XIII March 2003 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XIV March 2003 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XV March 2003 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XVI March 2003 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XVII March 2003 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XVIII March 2003 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XIX March 2003 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XX March 2003 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XXI March 2003 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan XXII March 2003 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Various March 2003 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Department of Defense April 2003 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Millennium Challenge Account April 2003 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Social Security April 2003 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Taxes April 2003 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Various April 2003 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - FCC Regulations May 2003 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Federal Law Enforcement Officers May 2003 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Gun Control May 2003 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Medicare May 2003 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Millennium Challenge Account May 2003 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Pension Reform May 2003 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Taxes May 2003 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Various May 2003 (Box-folder 20:13)
    - Animal Rights June 2003 (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Asbestos June 2003 (Box-folder 20:15)
    - Broad-Based Stock Option Plan Transparency Act June 2003 (Box-folder 20:16)
    - District of Columbia Statehood June 2003 (Box-folder 20:17)
    - English Language Unity Act June 2003 (Box-folder 20:18)
    - Interstate Waste June 2003 (Box-folder 20:19)
    - Iraq June 2003 (Box-folder 20:20)
    - Jet Noise June 2003 (Box-folder 20:21)
    - Medical Research June 2003 (Box-folder 20:22)
    - Medicare June 2003 (Box-folder 20:23)
    - Military Exemptions to Environmental Laws June 2003 (Box-folder 20:24)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits June 2003 (Box-folder 20:25)
    - Millennium Challenge Account June 2003 (Box-folder 20:26)
    - Naturally Occurring Retirement Communities (NORCS) June 2003 (Box-folder 20:27)
    - SBA 504 Loan Program June 2003 (Box-folder 20:28)
    - Social Security / Medicare June 2003 (Box-folder 20:29)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan June 2003 (Box-folder 20:30)
    - Taxes June 2003 (Box-folder 20:31)
    - Various June 2003 (Box-folder 20:32)
    - Army Watercraft Contracting July 2003 (Box-folder 20:33)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation July 2003 (Box-folder 20:34)
    - Fair Labor Standards July 2003 (Box-folder 20:35)
    - Interstate Waste July 2003 (Box-folder 20:36)
    - Iraq July 2003 (Box-folder 20:37)
    - Media Rights July 2003 (Box-folder 20:38)
    - Military / Veteran's Benefits July 2003 (Box-folder 20:39)
    - School Readiness Act July 2003 (Box-folder 20:40)
    - Various July 2003 (Box-folder 20:41)
    - Airline Pensions August 2003 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - American Horse Slaughter Prevention Act August 2003 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation August 2003 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Defense Commissary Agency (DeCA) August 2003 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Interstate Waste August 2003 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Iraq August 2003 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Medicare August 2003 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - National Farm Workers' Job Program (NFJP) August 2003 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Special Operations Forces (SOF) Retirement August 2003 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan August 2003 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Taxes August 2003 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Transportation August 2003 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Various August 2003 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Airline Pensions September 2003 (Box-folder 21:14)
    - Army Reserve September 2003 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - Concurrent Receipt of Military and Retired Pay and VA Disability Compensation September 2003 (Box-folder 21:16)
    - Interstate Waste September 2003 (Box-folder 21:17)
    - Iraq September 2003 (Box-folder 21:18)
    - Realty Regulations September 2003 (Box-folder 21:19)
    - Transportation September 2003 (Box-folder 21:20)
    - Various September 2003 (Box-folder 21:21)
    - American Horse Slaughter Prevention Act October 2003 (Box-folder 21:22)
    - FCC Regulations October 2003 (Box-folder 21:23)
    - Gay Marriage October 2003 (Box-folder 21:24)